~Brought to you by Crunchyroll.com~!
(大蛇丸)それで？
And...?
(カブト)はい
幽鬼丸の力に問題はないでしょう。
Yes, there should be no problem
with Yuukimaru's strength.
All that remains is
to modify the drug.
あとは 薬を調整するだけです。
(大蛇丸)いつ完成するの？
When will that be completed?
そう時間は かかりませんよ。
It won't take very long.
(大蛇丸)なら 紅蓮と幽鬼丸を
先に出発させなさい。
Then order Guren and Yuukimaru
to set out ahead.
(カブト)以前も言いましたが
大丈夫ですか あの女？
I know I've asked before,
but are you sure about that woman?
フフフ… しかたないのよ。
We have no choice.
これは
紅蓮にしかできないことだから。
This is something
only Guren can do.
紅蓮と幽鬼丸の力が
一つになって➡
This strategy will bear fruit
once Guren and Yuukimaru's powers
become one.
初めて この作戦は実を結ぶのよ。
フッ…。
(紅蓮)
いつまで私を待たせる気だ！
How long are you going
to make me wait?
フッ… もう待たなくてもいい。
No more waiting.
大蛇丸様の命令が出た。
Lord Orochimaru has given his order.
本当か！
Really?!
《単純なヤツめ》
So naïve.
幽鬼丸！
Yuukimaru!
(幽鬼丸)どこかに帰るの？
そこは ボクの帰る場所？
Are we returning somewhere?
Will that be my home?
なんだ コイツは？
Who is this kid?
You're taking him.
This boy.
お前が連れていくのは この子だ。
私に ガキのお守りを
しろってのかよ！
You expect me to babysit?
フン… さっそく文句か。
Already complaining?
大蛇丸様への忠誠は
ウソなのか？
Were you lying about being loyal
to Lord Orochimaru?
Although, with that attitude,
no child will take to you.
まぁ お前の がさつさでは
子供に好かれはしまいがな。
大蛇丸様のそばに仕えてるだけで
調子に乗るな。
Don't act smug just because
you're Lord Orochimaru's aide.
キサマなど いつでも殺せるんだ。
I can kill you anytime.
《なるほど
手近にある物質を 瞬時に結晶化。
I see. She's able to instantly
crystallize anything that's nearby.
丸腰に見えて コイツの周りは
武器だらけってことか。
Although she looks unarmed,
everything around her is a weapon.
これが 晶遁…。
So that is the Crystal Style.
大蛇丸様も 一目置くわけだな》
No wonder she caught
Lord Orochimaru's eye.
きっと ボクが死んだら➡
If I die, your reincarnation
won't go well.
お前の転生も
うまくはいかないぞ。
(カブト)大蛇丸様と
ひとつになりたいんだろう？
You want to become one
with Lord Orochimaru, don't you?
きれい…。
So pretty!
What're you saying?
(紅蓮)お前 何言ってんだ？
もっと降らないのかな？
ワケのわかんねえヤツだ。
Isn't it going to rain more?
Humph, what a weird kid.
フフフ… いいコンビだな。
You make a nice pair.
おっと ボクは すぐに追いつく。
幽鬼丸と先に出発してくれ。
Whoa.
I'll catch up right away.
So go on ahead with Yuukimaru.
チッ… まあいい。
All right.
だが 私に ふざけた態度を取ると
許さないよ。
But if he gets wise with me,
I'll let 'im have it.
気をつけろ。 あの辺りに
何者かが近づいている。
Be careful. Someone's approaching
from over that way.
なんだと!?
なぜ お前がそんなことを？
What?! How would you know that?
I didn't tell you, did I?
言ってなかったかな？
お前のアジトに向かう途中➡
On the way to your hideout,
I took care of an Anbu Black Ops
あの辺りを探っていた
木ノ葉の暗部を１人 始末した。
from the Hidden Leaf Village
who was checking out the area
すでに木ノ葉が動いているはずだ。
The Leaf Village is sure
to be on the move.
相手にするのは厄介だ。
適当に撒くといい。
You don't want to get involved
with them.
Make sure you give them the slip.
そんなことは私が決める。
(カブト)幽鬼丸の任務に失敗すれば➡
I'll be the judge of that.
Remember, if you fail
in this mission with Yuukimaru,
お前の転生の話も
なくなることを忘れるな。
all discussion of
your reincarnation ends.
A Night of Rain
《木ノ葉か…》
The Hidden Leaf...
《まさか あの連中 木ノ葉に
寝返ったりしないだろうね》
Those guys! They'd better not betray me
and run to the Hidden Leaf!
ボクは帰れるのかな…。
Am I going home?
I hope I can return home...
帰れるといいなぁ。
But is there a place I can return to?
でも ボクには
帰る場所があるのかな…。
((ナルト : 思ってるヤツがいる所が
帰ってくる場所なんだ！))
A place where someone thinks of you,
that's where home is.
きっと あるよね。
I'm sure there is.
(リンジ)これを見ろ。
コイツは犬の爪跡だ。
Look over here.
These are dog tracks.
犬か…。
A dog...
《まずったな》
That was a bad move.
(シノ)反応が感じとれないくらい
弱くなっている。
They've become so weak,
I can't feel their response.
(シノ)見つけた。
Found one!
よし 卵を持っている。
All right! It's got eggs.
孵化できれば…。
If I can make them hatch...
だいたいよぉ
ガマオヤビンの息子なのに➡
I don't get it!
Why can't the son of
the Chief Toad use Water Style?!
どうして
水遁が できねえんだってばよ！
The Chief Toad!
ガマオヤビンてば！
Liquid Bullets!
((ガマ文太 : 鉄砲玉！))
He uses Water Style amazingly!
って すんげえ
水遁の使い手じゃねえかよ！
(ガマ吉)んなこと言ったって➡
Well, if I can't do it,
I can't do it.
できねえもんは
できねえんじゃけん。
So quit harping about that!
ウダウダ言うな。
何だ それ!?
- What?!
- Don't say, "what"!
何じゃい！
(木ノ葉丸)まぁまぁ ナルト兄ちゃん。
Oh come on, Brother Naruto.
ここは ガマ竜さんの修業から
やるしかないぞ コレ！
You'll just have to make do with
Mr. Gamatatsu's way of training.
小僧！
オメエ よう物事わかっとるのぉ。
Boy, now there's a kid
who understands.
…って そんなヒマ
あるわけねえだろ！
I don't have that kind of time!
イヤなら こっちも オメエの修業に
付き合うのは やめじゃ。
Well, if you're not interested,
then I'll quit training you!
Ask Mr. Gamariki to help you.
また ガマ力さんに
手伝ってもらうんじゃのう。
((ガマ力 : イヤ～ン ウッフ～ン))
Oh no...!
わかった。
やっぱり ガマ竜の修業に➡
Got it... I'll train with Gamatatsu,
after all.
オレも付き合うってばよ。
Okay. As long as you understand.
おうか。 まぁ わかれば
いいんじゃけん。 わかれば。
So how do you start
Water Style Jutsu?
で 水遁の術って
何からやるんだ？
(ガマ竜)あ…。
改めて言われれば➡
Well, frankly, I'm not sure...
どうやっていいのか
わからんのう。
あ そうか！
水遁だから とりあえず➡
I see!
It's Water Style, so we should start
by drinking water.
水を飲めばいいんじゃねえか？
I see...
なるほど。
Oh! Yes, I see!
あぁ そうじゃのう。
え～!?
(ヌラリ)
敵が うろついてるって 本当？
Is it true the enemy
is prowling around?
間違いない。
この山に潜伏している。
I'm sure of it.
They're hiding in this mountain.
(キギリ)いったい 誰なんです？
Just who are they?
わからん。 大蛇丸のアジトを
探していたとなると➡
I don't know.
But if they're searching for
Orochimaru's hideout...
暁か… 木ノ葉か…。
Either the Akatsuki...
or the Hidden Leaf.
(ヌラリ)どうする？
こっちから仕掛ける？
What'll we do? Should we attack?
紅蓮さんが いないとなると➡
Without Guren, there's no guarantee
that we can pull it off.
こっちも
無事で済むという保証はない。
(ゴズ)意外だな。
(リンジ)ん？ 何がだ？
I was wrong...
About what?
I figured this was your chance...
to make a run for it.
てっきり オレは 今こそ➡
お前たちが逃げ出すかと
思っていた。
逃げ出すだと？
A run for it?
大蛇丸の情報を手土産に➡
Your chance to run over
to the Hidden Leaf's side
木ノ葉に取り入る チャンスだ。
with information
about Orochimaru as a gift.
フン… なるほどね。
I see. Well, I never gave it
a thought...
そんな考えは これっぽっちも
思いつかなかった。
フッ そうか オメエさん
木ノ葉に投降したいのか。
I get it. You wanna turn yourself in
to the Hidden Leaf?
そんなつもりは毛頭ない。
Not at all.
なら オメエさんが
紅蓮さんに従う理由は何だ？
Then what's your reason
for sticking with Guren?
個人的な理由だ。
It's personal.
ほう。
Hmm...?
ったく 私一人なら➡
Cripes...
If I were alone, I would have
already reached my destination.
とっくに 目的地に
着いてるってのに…。
(幽鬼丸)ボク あそこは
もう行きたくない。
I don't want to go there anymore.
頭痛くなるし…。
イヤだな 帰りたい。
I get headaches...
No, I want to go back.
でも ボクの帰るところ
ないんだった。
But I don't have a place to return to.
あ でも この前会った人は➡
Oh...but that person said...
If someone is thinking about me...
that's the place to go home to.
誰かが
ボクのことを思ってくれたとき➡
そこが ボクの帰る場所になるんだ
って言ってて…。
けど ボクのことを
思ってくれる人は➡
But how do I go about getting
someone to think about me?
どうやって つくるのかな？
(紅蓮)ベラベラしゃべってないで
もっと速く歩けないのか！
Can't you quit babbling
and start walking faster?
《ったく なんだ このガキは…》
Cripes! Just what's with this kid?
赤い椿か 白い椿
どっちが好き？
A red camellia or a white one.
Which do you prefer?
A camellia...
椿。
椿？
Camellia?
それ。
That...
あぁ 確かに これは椿だ。
Oh. Yes, this is a camellia, all right.
椿が好き？
椿…。
Do you like camellias?
Camellias...
I don't like camellias.
椿なんて 好きじゃない。
This is just coincidence.
たまたまだ。
あっ おい！
Hey!
どうした!?
ハァ ハァ…。
What's the matter?!
ハァ ハァ ハァ…。
クッソ…。
Damn!
Damn! There's no way we can go back
to the hideout in this rain.
クソッ この雨じゃ アジトに
引き返すわけにもいかないし。
(幽鬼丸)うぅ… 寒い。
I-It's cold.
What? You're cold?
なに!? 寒いのか？
あっ 熱が！
A fever...!
(ヤマト)お呼びでしょうか。
You summoned me?
Yamato, I want you to go
and assist Team Kakashi.
(綱手)ヤマト。 カカシ班の
援護に向かってもらいたい。
(ヤマト)カカシ先輩の？
Kakashi Senpai?
I heard it was just a scouting mission.
ただの探索だと聞いていますが➡
何かあったんですか？
(綱手)敵とニアミスしたらしい。
Has something happened?
The problem is that
they had a run-in with the enemy.
ただ その敵が問題だ。
(綱手)これまで
見たこともない術を使う。
This foe uses a Jutsu
we've never seen before.
見たことのない術…。
A Jutsu we've never seen before?
We don't understand everything
about it yet.
まだ はっきりしたことは
言えない。
今 カカシが送ってきたサンプルを➡
I'm having the sample Kakashi sent
analyzed right away.
急いで分析させているところだ。
Who shall I take?
誰を連れて行きます？
Sai who can search from the sky,
and Sakura in case anyone is injured.
空からの索敵のために サイ➡
ケガ人が出たときのために
サクラを同行しろ。
そのサクラだが 私の仕事で
出ている。
But Sakura has gone on
an errand for me.
明朝 戻ってくる予定だ。
She's to return at dawn.
Set out as soon as
Sakura comes back.
サクラが戻りしだい 出発しろ。
わかりました。
でも 大蛇丸がらみだと➡
Understood.
But if this involves Orochimaru,
won't Naruto want to go too?
ナルトは 行きたがるでしょうね。
Now listen! Naruto is not
to find about about this.
いいか このことは
絶対に ナルトに知らせるな！
(カカシ)どうだ 何か見つかったか？
How did it go? Find anything?
No, nothing...
(ヒナタ)ダメです 何も。
I came up with nothing too.
(キバ)こっちも まるでダメだ。
Especially when it rains,
特に 雨に降られちゃ➡
these conditions make it impossible
to catch any scents.
オレたちの鼻には
不利な条件が重なるぜ。
進展なしか…。
So...no progress at all.
うっ！
Huh?!
Even the bats are inside...
(キバ)コウモリも雨宿りか…。
Huh? Bats?!
コウモリ。
(ヒナタ)
私 もう一度 探索に行ってきます。
I'll go out and search once more.
No wait! Don't move.
いや 待て。 動くな。
え？
What's the matter, Kiba?
どうした キバ？
Well, I've been thinking about it
this whole time...
いや ずっと考えてたんだ。
犬笛の謎をな。
About that mysterious
dog whistle.
犬笛の謎？
The mysterious dog whistle?
Yeah... There's an animal that uses
ultrasonic waves
ああ 犬笛の周波数と同じ
超音波を使う動物がいる。
with the same frequency
as a dog whistle...
コイツだ。
These guys here.
なるほど。
I see.
ヤツらは
コウモリを操っているというんだな。
You're saying the enemy
is manipulating a bat?
But which bat?
でも どのコウモリが？
Well, I don't know that.
さあな そこまでは わからねえが
闇雲に動けば➡
The more we move in the shadows,
余計にヤツらに
居場所を知られることになる。
the greater the chance
of our being detected.
(キバ)いや
すでに監視されてるかもしれねえ。
In fact, they may already
have spotted us.
里で分析してもらっている
結晶の結果さえ出れば➡
Once the crystal sample
we sent to the village is analyzed,
なにか手段を講じられるが…。
we'll know what steps
can be taken next.
(カカシ)ここは シノの蟲に
期待するしかないか。
Right now, we have to place
our hopes on Shino's insects.
ハァ ハァ…。
《紅蓮 : 大蛇丸様に吉報を
届けなきゃならないってのに。
I have to deliver good news
to Lord Orochimaru...!
今 コイツに死なれちゃ困るんだ。
いいか 死ぬなよ》
I can't have you die right now!
You got that? Don't die!
(キギリ)遅えな まだかよ。
She's late!
When's she coming back?
Yeah, she should have returned by now.
(リンジ)
確かに もう戻ってもいい頃だな。
《リンジとゴズも
連れてくるんだったな》
I should've brought Rinji and Gozu.
((気をつけろ。 あの辺りに
何者かが近づいている))
Be careful. Someone's approaching
from over that way.
《こんなところで グズグズしてる
わけにはいかないってのに》
I can't waste time
in a place like this...
大丈夫か？
Are you all right?
あったかい。
So warm.
(紅蓮)しまった！
Damn!
♬(笹笛)
(紅蓮)何をしている？
What are you doing?
紅蓮さん…。
Guren...
もう 具合はいいのか？
Are you feeling better?
お前に いなくなられちゃ
困るからな。
I can't have you disappearing
like that.
お前は大蛇丸様からの
大事な預かりものだ。
Lord Orochimaru entrusted you to me.
(紅蓮)それは？
What's that?
かあさまに…。
My mom...
そういえば お前 家族は？
By the way, where's...your family?
My mother...didn't return...
かあさまは…
帰ってこなかった…。
だから… ボクの帰る場所は…。
So...I don't have anywhere to go.
椿… 好きなんだろう？
Camellias... You like them, right?
この椿は決して枯れはしない。
This camellia will never wither.
私が死なないかぎりはな。
As long as I'm alive.
(紅蓮)行くぞ。
Let's go.
Is this the newly hatched insect
you were talking about?
ハハッ… いいこだぞ～ 赤丸！
しかし 赤丸ってば
ホント デカくなったよなぁ…。
With this insect,
we can go up against
that Crystal Style Jutsu, right?
そうかぁ？
お前さ ホントに赤丸の成長とか➡
There's a good chance
it has a high resistance level, however...
全然 気づかなかったのかよ？
There's not enough to use
in actual combat...
ん～ そうだな 言われてみれば…。
Damn! And I thought we had
counter measures to fight them...
どうだ？ かゆいところはないか？
赤丸。
(赤丸)ワン！
No, it's too early to give up.
(キバ)若干 シャンプーの減りが…➡
- Huh?
- You have a plan?
早くなった気はしたな…
それに…。
Yes, give me some time.
どうだ？ 気持いいか？ 赤丸。
ワンッ！
Next time:
"The Two Charms"
ブラッシングで取れる毛の量が
増えた気もするような…。
Good boy, Akamaru!
あとは…。
さぁこい 赤丸！ 散歩にいくぞ！
(キバ)赤丸を頭に乗せた途端➡
急に意識が ぶっ飛んだことが
あったっけ…。
でも まぁ 些細なことだしな。
んなワケ ねえだろ！
だって 昔から 白いし
フカフカだし 鼻黒いし…。
ワン！
これで気づけ
って言われても➡
困るよな？ 赤丸！
ワン！
うん。 何か もう…➡
どうでもいいってばよ。